Theresa Wolfson Papers 5216
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Theresa Wolfson Papers
1880-1970
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Wolfson, Theresa
5216
40.61 cubic feet
35.6 linear ft.
First drafts, manuscripts for publication, papers (documents).
This collection is a portion of Wolfson's papers contain manuscripts and research materials for a project (1947-48) interviewing labor leaders for "Philosophy and Labor." Interviewees included leaders from the following unions: San Francisco Labor Council, San Francisco Labor Research Bureau, ILGWU's San Francisco Joint Board, California State Council of Retail Clerks, and Bay District Joint Council of Building Service Employees.
3834254
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 16, 2008
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 21, 2017
Biographical / Historical
Theresa Wolfson was a professor of economics and industrial relations, arbitrator and mediator.
Chronology
1897: Born July 19, 1897
1917: A.B. Adelphi College
1923: A.M. Columbia University
1921-27: Teacher of workers classes for Educational Department of ILGWU and lecturer at Brookwood Labor College
1924: PhD. Brookings Graduate School
1926: Teacher of Economics at Bryn Mawr Summer School
1928-30: Instructor of Economics, Hunter College, Brooklyn Branch
1931-32: Teacher of Economics at Summer School for Office Workers, Oberlin College
1936: Teacher of Economics at Summer School for Office Workers, Northwestern University
1946: Lecturer on Labor Problems, Encampment for Citizenship, Riverdale, NY
1949: Lecturer on Labor Problems, Summer School for Office Workers, Columbus, Ohio
1949-50: Lecturer at NYC Graduate School on International Labor
1950: Lectured at Haverford College, Pa., Labor Education Association
1952: Lecturer, Cornell University, NYSSILR
1959-72: Professor of Economics and Labor Relations, Brooklyn College
1972: Died on June 3, 1972
Scope and Contents
The papers of Theresa Wolfson consist of correspondence (1919-1970) documenting professional and personal involvements with students, colleagues, and friends; Brooklyn College materials (1924-1970) documenting her teaching experience and involvement with various College committees; arbitration and mediation files for cases handled by Wolfson (1942-1969), particularly in the chemical, machinery, and newspaper industries; drafts and manuscripts by Wolfson and her colleagues (1925-1960); book and article reviews by Wolfson (1936-1951); materials relating to Wolfson's labor leader project (1947-1948); research materials and correspondence (1746-1967) for a book on Frances Wright, which Wolfson co-authored with A.J.G. Perkins, transferred to Cornell's Rare and Manuscript Collection, as collection no.6934; materials on schools and organizations involved in workers' education (1920-1961); and subject files relating chiefly to economics and labor (1880-1969).
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arrangement
Series I. CORRESPONDENCE, 1919-1970
Series II. BROOKLYN COLLEGE (also includes Sarah Lawrence College), 1924-1970
Sub-Series A. Minutes Sub-Series B. Committees Sub-Series C. Courses Sub-Series D. Examinations Sub-Series E. Subject Files Sub-Series F. Sarah Lawrence College
Series III. ARBITRATION AND MEDIATION FILES, 1924-1969
Series IV. LITERARY MANUSCRIPTS, 1925-1960
Sub-Series A. Drafts of books, articles, etc. Sub-Series B. Reviews of books and articles
Series V. SUBJECT FILES
Sub-Series A. Fanny Wright Sub-Series B. Files on workers' education, 1930-1961 Sub-Series C. Japanese Sabbatic Sub-Series D. Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1920-1970
Series VI. Pamphlets
Sub-Series Pamphlets and Articles by Wolfson
Series VII. MISCELLANEOUS
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Cases; Arbitration, Industrial -- Chemical industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Machine industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Newspaper publishing -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Paper industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Retail trade -- New York (State) -- New York; Arbitration, Industrial -- Social workers -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Teachers -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Textile industry -- United States; Arbitrators, Industrial.; Collective bargaining -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; College teachers.; Employee fringe benefits -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Employees, Dismissal of -- Arbitration, Industrial -- New York (State) -- New York; Employees, Dismissal of -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Hours of labor -- Arbitration, Industrial -- New York (State) -- New York; Health insurance -- New York (State) -- New York; Working class -- Health and hygiene -- United States; Labor economics.; Layoffs -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Mediation and conciliation, Industrial -- United States -- Cases; Position classification -- Arbitration, Industrial -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor unions -- Officials and employees; Labor unions -- Officials and employees -- United States; Teachers' unions -- United States; Wages -- Arbitration, Industrial -- New York (State) -- New York; Wages -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Wages -- Retail trade -- New York (State) -- New York; Wages -- Women -- United States; Women labor union members -- United States; Workers' education -- United States; Workers' education -- Women -- United States; Working conditions -- Arbitration, Industrial -- New York (State) -- New York; World War, 1939-1945 -- Women -- United States; World War, 1939-1945 -- War work; AFSCME; Allen-Stevens Corporation; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America; American Civil Liberties Union; American Federation of Labor. Central Labor Council of Alameda County; American Federation of Labor. Committee on Education; American Labor Education Service; Amperex Electronics Company; Barnard Summer School for Women Workers in Industry; Bay District Joint Council of Building Service Employees; Brooklyn College; Brooklyn College. Department of Economics. Administration; Brookwood Labor College (Katonah, N.Y.); Bryn Mawr College; Bryn Mawr Summer School; California State Council of Retail Clerks; California State Federation of Labor; Civic Club (New York, N.Y.). Committee on Labor Education; Community and Social Agency Employees Union; International Association of Machinists; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America; International Chemical Workers Union (1944- ); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Educational Department; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. San Francisco Joint Board; International Longshoremen's Association; International Typographical Union; Michigan Workers' Education Service; National League Summer School; New York (N.Y.). Board of Education; New York (State). Temporary Commission Against Discrimination; Office and Professional Employees International Union; Oil Workers International Union; Macy's (Firm); Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union; San Francisco Labor Council; San Francisco Labor Research Bureau; Southern School for Workers; Summer School for Office Workers, Inc.; Textile Workers Union of America; Trade Union Educational League (U.S.); United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America; United Packinghouse Workers of America; United States. National Recovery Administration; United Steelworkers of America; Workers' Defense League; Young Women's Christian Association of the U.S.A; Alexis, Marcus; Bentham, Jeremy, 1748-1832; Chamberlain, Neil W. (Neil Wolverton), 1915-; Cohn, Fannia M. (Fannia Mary), 1885-; Coit, Eleanor G.; D'Arusmont, Phiquepal, (William Phiquepal); D'Arusmont, Sylvie; Draper, Theodore, 1912-; Epstein, Abraham, 1892-1942; Epstein, Irving; Flower, George, 1788-1862; Forgang, Isak; Fretageot, Marie Louise Duclos, d. 1833; Gompers, Samuel, 1850-1924; Jones, Brownie Lee; Lafayette, Marie Joseph Paul Yves Roch Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de, 1757-1834; Millar, Mrs. Craig; Milne, James; Neufeld, Maurice F.; Owen, Robert Dale, 1801-1877; Pope, Helen; Pope, William; Richardson, James; Roscoe, William; Starr, Mark, 1894-; Wilkes, Charles; Wolfson, Theresa, 1897-1972; Wright, Camilla; Wright, Frances, 1795-1852; Wright, Richard, b. 1794
3834254
- Series I. CORRESPONDENCE, 1919-1970
  Scope and Contents
  Consists chiefly of correspondence with former students regarding letters of recommendation; letters concerning book reviews and articles; letters concerning the scheduling of lectures and speaking engagements; and correspondence with colleagues and friends. Chief correspondents include Marcus Alexis (associate professor, DePaul University); Mae Bagwell (American Nurses' Association); Carolyn Balderidge; June Beauvais (assistant secretary of the Florida Nurses Association); Neil W. Chamberlain (Graduate School of Business, Columbia University); Fannia Cohn (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union); Eleanor G. Coit (director, American Labor Education Service); Theodore Draper (author); Irving Epstein (Textile Workers of America); Isak Forgang (Kibbutz Chatzor, Tel Aviv, Israel); Sol Jacobson (co-ordinator of Industrial Relations, Brooklyn College); Brownie Lee Jones (program associate, American Labor Education Service); Goodman L. Klang; Maurice Neufeld (professor, Cornell University); Mary Palevsky (American Joint Distribution Committee); William and Helen Pope; and Mark Starr (educational director, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union). Also included is a letter (1923) from Abraham Epstein (executive secretary, Old Age Assistance Commission, Harrisburg); a letter (1923) from Samuel Gompers (president of the American Federation of Labor) regarding Wolfson's thesis "Women in Trade Unions"; numerous reactions and criticisms fromWolfson's colleagues regarding her thesis; and letters concerning the Summer School for Women Workers in Industry at Bryn Mawr College (1931).
  - Routine, 1919-1923 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
  - Letter to Theresa Wolfson from Fannia Cohn, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    3/11/24; re plan on "Women in Industry," discusses appointments of women for Executive Secretary position
  - Routine, 1925-1930 (Box 1, Folder 5-10)
  - Letter to Theresa Wolfson from Fannia Cohn, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    3/17, 3/21/31; re general situation and confusion in the ILGWU Education Department mentioning Rose Schniederman, Mable Leslie, Elsie Gluck, Hilda Smith, and Rose Wortis
  - Letter to Theresa Wolfson from Carrie Glasser, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    with the LID in Charleston, W.Va. Describing discrimination against union people in mines in Gallagher County
  - Routine, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
  - Two letters from Theodore Draper, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    describing 11 hours of interviewing with Mr. Strasser of the Cigar Makers Union
  - Routine, 1936-1949 (Box 1, Folder 16-30)
  - Routine, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 1-6)
  - Routine, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 1-13)
  - Routine, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 1-12)
  - Routine, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 1-11)
  - Routine, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 1-9)
  - Correspondence, 1961-1964 (Box 7, Folder 1-10)
  - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 8, Folder 1-8)
  - Undated correspondence (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Series II. BROOKLYN COLLEGE (also includes Sarah Lawrence College), 1924-1970
  Includes course materials as well as committee and departmental files from Wolfson's teaching career at Brooklyn College and Sarah Lawrence College. Includes minutes of the Brooklyn College Department of Economics (1950-1955) and minutes of the Brooklyn College Faculty Council (1941-1964). Also files on several Brooklyn College faculty committees on which Wolfson served (1942-1965) and course materials and lecture notes for courses taught in economics and labor relations (1932-1966). Professor Wolfson also maintained a file, included herein, for Sarah Lawrence College during the period she taught there (1967-1970).
  - Sub-Series A. Minutes
    - Minutes, Department of Economics, 1950-1955 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, Faculty Council, 1941-1964 (Box 9, Folder 2-5)
      also includes memos, agendas, reports, and lists of graduates
  - Sub-Series B. Committees
    - Area Studies Committee, 1949-1960 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - College Scholarship Committee, 1957-1959 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Academic Appointments, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Business Enterprises, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Committee on Collective Bargaining, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
    - Committee on Course and Standing, 1954-1956 (Box 10, Folder 4-6)
    - Committee on Curriculum - Social Sciences, 1950-1952 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Evaluation, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Examinations, 1942-1944 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Committee on Graduate Courses, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Committee on Graduate Courses - Standing, 1952-1954 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Committee on Long-Term Curriculum Study, 1948-1952 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Committee on Multiple Positions, 1945-1947 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Orientation and Counseling, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Review, 1944-1947 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Committee on Social Science Course, 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
    - Committee on Studen Personnel, 1942-1946 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Committee on Tenure, 1955-1957 (Box 11, Folder 7-8)
    - Committee on Improvement of Teaching, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Committee to Seek A President, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1946-1949 (Box 11, Folder 11-12)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1950-1956 (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
    - Departmental Evaluation Committee, 1950-1953 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Committee, 1953-1965 (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
    - Faculty Day Committee, 1958-1961 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Graduate Committee, 1954-1964 (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
    - Legislative Committee, 1950-1953 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Promotion Committee, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series C. Courses
    Arranged alphabetically by title. Includes course outlines, mimeos, lecture notes, bibliographies, teaching aids, and reading lists.
    - Arbitration (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Consumer Economics (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Corporations and Trusts (Box 13, Folder 3-11)
    - Economic Theory (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Economics (Box 14, Folder 2-10)
    - Economics I (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
    - Economics 114 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Economics 321 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Economics 323G (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Economics 324 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Economics - European Labor Markets (Box 15, Folder 9-10)
    - Economics of Socialism (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
    - Government (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Government and Labor (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Government and Sociology (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Government in Industrial Relations (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - History (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Labor Problems (Box 16, Folder 8-10)
    - Social Science (Box 17, Folder 1-3)
    - Statistics (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
    - Trade Unionism (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series D. Examinations
    Includes copies of examination papers given by Professor Wofson in courses which she taught.
    - Exams (Box 17, Folder 7-8)
    - Exams (Box 18, Folder 1-4)
    - Miscellaneous lecture notes, outlines, etc. (Box 18, Folder 5-7)
  - Sub-Series E. Subject Files
    Includes miscellaneous Brooklyn College-related materials: memos, reports, students' files, and conference information.
    - American Association of University Professors (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Audio-Visual (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Berkeley, California (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Brooklyn College - 25th anniversary (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Bureau of Economic Research (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - College By-Laws (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - College Lecture Series (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - College Teachers Union (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Commencement (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Communism (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Conference - Brooklyn Human Relations (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Conference - Legislative Conference City University (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Conference - Regional Conference on Higher Education (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Conference - United Parent's Association (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Cornell University - Lecture (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Dress Code (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Economic Education (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Employer-Labor Policies (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Faculty Day Committee (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Financial Aid (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Kapp, K. William (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Labor Group (Box 20, Folder 3-4)
    - Memos - General (Box 20, Folder 5-8)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Promotion to Associate Professor (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Publications (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Student Organizations (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Students - Cost of Living (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Students - Essay Contest (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Students - Evaluation Study (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Students (Former) - Articles, etc. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Students - Forms, reports, analysis (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Students - Grade Information (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Students - Placement (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Students - Protest Movement (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Students - Roster (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Students - Thesis Supervision (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Studesnt - Vita (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Taxation (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - United Federation of College Teachers (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Viet Nam (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series F. Sarah Lawrence College
    Papers collected while teaching economics on a half-time basis at Sarah Lawrence College, 1967-1970. Includes inter-office memos, correspondence, course outlines and school publications.
    - Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Student Information, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Invitation to inauguration of new President of Sarah Lawrence, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Memos, 1967-1970 (Box 22, Folder 4-8)
    - Course Outlines (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Publications (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Series III. ARBITRATION AND MEDIATION FILES, 1924-1969
  Includes correspondence, mss. notes, awards, statements, clippings, and papers on arbitration and mediation cases handled by Wolfson, 1942-1969. Wolfson arbitrated in the chemical, machinery, and newspaper industries, among others. Major cases include Allen-Stevens Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists (IAM) (1960) regarding discharge; Amperek Electronics Company vs. IAM (1958) regarding discharge and sick leave; Community and Social Agency Employees vs. Professional Employees (1962) regarding contract interpretation on dismissals; DeWald Radio Manufacturing Company vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (1943) regarding contract renewal; Eastern Bias Manufacturing Company vs. Textile Workers of America (1958) regarding wage increase and backpay; Eaton Manufacturing Company Incorporated vs. IAM (1954) regarding sick leave; H.M. Storms Company vs. United Paperworkers (1957) regarding layoff; R.H. Macy and Company vs. United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees (1944) regarding wage increase; Manhattan News Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT) (1954) regarding layoff; Mobilization for Youth vs. IBT (l966) regarding discharge; New York City Board of Education vs. American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (1967, 1969) regarding discharge and transfer; Reilly Tar and Chemical Corporation vs. Chemical Workers Union (1944) regarding wages and retroactive pay, night shift bonuses, vacations, paid holidays, and reporting pay.
  - Allen-Stevens Corporation, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - American Bedding, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - American Numbering Machine Co., 1968 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Amperex Electronics, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Bendix Aviation, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Community and Social Agency Employees, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - DeWald Radio, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Eastern Bias Manufacturing Co., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Eyton Manufacturing Co., 1954 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - H.M. Storms, Co., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Irving Milgrim, Inc., 1959 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - J.H. Gertner, Jr., Inc, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Kleinbro Shoes, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Macy and Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Manhattan News Co., 1954 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Michaels Brothers, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Mobilization for Youth, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Mt. Hope Cemetery, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - NYC Board of Education, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Reilly Tar and Chemical, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - United Packinghouse Workers - Meat Packing Industry, 1945-1950 (Box 24, Folder 3-4)
  - Western Union Telegraph Co., 1948-1966 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration - General, 1950-1962 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Series IV. LITERARY MANUSCRIPTS, 1925-1960
  Drafts and manuscripts of books and articles by Wolfson and her colleagues dealing with the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, American labor, unemployment, Jewish women in the American labor movement, the National Recovery Administration, economic security, socialism, Soviet unemployment insurance, the Trade Union Educational League, wages, women, workers' health, industrial conflict, industrial unionism, the Rifton Strike, and Samuel Gompers. Also includes project outline, manuscript chapter drafts, and interview notes for a project by Wolfson (1947-1948) of interviewing labor leaders for "Philosophy and Labor". The project involved interviewing 100 individuals in the American Federation of Labor (A.F.of L.), the Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO), and independent unions to explore matters of concern to organized labor. Leaders from the following unions were interviewed: A.F.of L. Central Labor Council, United Automobile Workers, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, International Longshoremen's Union, International Association of Machinists, Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, Michigan Workers' Education Service, Oil Workers' International Union, United Packinghouse Workers of America, International Typographical Union, California State Council of Retail Clerks, Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, United Rubber Workers, Bay District Joint Council of Building Service Employees, San Francisco Labor Council, Labor Research Bureau and California State Federation of Labor, United Steelworkers of America, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, and Textile Workers' Union of North America.
  - Sub-Series A. Drafts of books, articles, etc.
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers and Stabilization (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - American Labor Looked at the World (Box 25, Folder 2-3)
    - A Backward Look and a Great Leap Forward (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Brief Report on a Method of Teaching Economics (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Changes in the Labor Force (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - CIO Plans and Policies (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Conversion of War to Peace Time Economy (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Defense of Workers Health (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Do you Know American Labor (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Economic Underwriting of the Constitution (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Estimates of Unemployment (Box 26, Folder 2)